<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
<text>
<body>
<div type="letter">
<opener>
<dateline>
<date when="1982-09-17">
9-17-82</date>
</dateline>
<salute>Hey! Hey! Tressy </salute>
</opener>
<note>
<p>
Today is Friday and it's night with nothing to watch on TV but reruns--so
</p>
<p>
<joke>A woman went to court for her third divorce, the Judge ask? Haven't you been here before? She said yes this is is my third divorce. My first husband was a shrink, all he wanted to do was talk about it, the second was a OBGYN all he wanted to do was look at it, the third was a pharmacy and he had to have a prescription to feel it, she was in trouble don’t you think? 
</joke>
<action>smile</action>
</p>
<p>Tressy you don't have to write every time I write you, once a mo will do, I won't be able to get the stamps this week but I'll get them, I'm planing to make you a cake and sent it soon.
</p>
</note>
<note>
<dateline>
<date when="1982-09-18">
9-17-82</date>
</dateline>
Boys! I’m tired, been running back and forth to the church: they had [an?] 200 lb Pig B.B.Q and I helped a little. I don’t think they liked it because I didn’t take any thing to go with it. I’m fixing my stuff for tomorrow, it's
<persName ref="#Preacher">Roosevelt's (Preacher's)</persName>
day I'm over the work in the kitchen, so I’m takeing stuff. You should have seen all the Brown’s the ones by birth and the ones that married into it, every one followed
<persName ref="#Hester">Hester</persName>
around like pup's. I wish have ask
<persName ref="#Diann_Logan">Diann</persName>
to help in the kitchen. I miss you and even today, I don’t know why I guess it’s because I don’t have any company—the chicken is happy now they have food, but the cat is in troble [trouble]. A dog or cat run him upon the house I Can hear him walking around. I’m watching meatball, I haven’t seen
<persName ref="#Trina_Logan">Tree </persName>Tree
yet.
<persName ref="#Gina_Logan">Gina</persName>
is playing softball. Oh yes I got up at 5:00 this morning to see
<rs type="event" ref="#Funeral">the funeral of Princess Grace</rs>
too sleepy to watch it at that time but just happent to see it at 4:00 this PM, it was sad I felt so sorry for her husband and daughters they cryed the whole time the other girl is still in the hospital. I’ll stop for tonight and look for some cross stitch for Chris. 
</note>
<note>
<date when="1982-09-19">
9-19-82</date>
<p>Oh Boy!</p>
<p>
I'm tired too-oo night, I worked in the kitchen.
<persName ref="#Mrs_Brown">Mrs Brown</persName>
and me worked the hole time. I'm glad its over. I'll never work in the kitcehn with 
<persName ref="#Mrs_Brown">John Edna</persName>
again. Never. 
<persName ref="#Laura_Freeman">Laura</persName>
said the--program was good. I could hear some of it but I'm glad its over.
</p>
<p>
Not much to write about I hope you got through the weekend fine. Everyone here doing fine.
</p>
<p>
<persName ref="#Beulah_Gaffney">Beulah</persName>
is home from the hospital. I just talk with her.
<persName ref="Wilma_Hamrick"> Wilma Hamrick</persName>
was as the church with two of
<persName ref="#Clyde">Clyde's</persName>
sisters
<persName ref="#Steve">Uncle Steve</persName>
and
<persName ref="#Plesent">Plesent</persName>
was there.</p>
<p>
I guess this is all for now. I'm dreading tomorrow its back to work
<advice>you just be good and be Tressy don't try to be anyone els, & try to know your friends. I believe you have a clear head and that will carry through whatever you put your heart and hands too, so just be you!
</advice>
I love you very very much man to little girl! Where did you get all that beautiful hair, girl. From daddy I guess because Mother have all of her’s. 
</p>
</note>
<closer>
<p>I love you, and we'll see you if you get home this weekend</p>
<p>Love always</p>
<signed>Mary--</signed>
</closer>
</div>
</body>
</text>
</TEI>
