<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
<text>
<body>
<div type="letter">
<opener>
<dateline>
<date when="1982-09-12">
9-12-82</date>
</dateline>
<salute>Dear Tressy,</salute>
</opener>
<p>
Well today is Sunday, and church is over, and I have nothing to do or any where to go, so I'll just set here and do what?
</p>
<p>
Hope you are getting use to be away from home and haveing a good time. Friday night some of the football team was in a wreck, some hurt bad was sent to
<placeName ref="#Spartanburg">Spartanburg,</placeName>
to a hospital one of the boys was
<persName ref="#Vincent_Logan">Vincent Logan</persName>
He is Ray's
brother,
they say he was the star player.
<persName ref="#Gina_Logan">Gina</persName>
is home she is going back to school and is going to leave the baby with 
<persName ref="Gearl_Logan">Gearl.</persName>
I haven't seen them yet, she'll be here until Oct. 1
</p>
<p>
<persName ref="#Johnie_M.">Johnie M.</persName>
and me worked at a wedding last night. I thought I would dream dishes the rest of the night. I got tired. We worked from 6 to 10. I needed the money
</p>
<p>
A message from the chicken's
<quote>come home we are hungry--haven't eaten since Friday. Come please.
</quote>
</p>
<p>
Not much to write about here is $4.00 can you buy stamps there, if so can you get a book for four dollars, if not I'll try to send you some next week. 
<advice>
Work hard and learn everything you can.
</advice>
I'm glad you are working that will keep some to keep from being homesick.
<advice>Just keep bussey at somethings, even if you have to make up somethings to do.
</advice>
</p>
<p>My spelling is afull but I hope you can make out what I'm saying.
</p>
<p>
<advice>Be good and work hard. I love you and so proud of you, because you are trying to make better your life so you won't have to wash dishes and make bed's and sweep nasty floors.
</advice>
<wish>
I wish I could have did more with my life
</wish>
</p>
<closer>
<p>I'll love you always</p>
<signed>Mary--(Grandmother)</signed>
</closer>
<postscript> 
<p>The boys was from the high school in
<placeName ref="Spindale">Spindale,</placeName>
haven't heard they're doing
</p>
<p>Mary</p>
</postscript>
</div>
</body>
</text>
</TEI>