<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
<text>
<body>
<div type="letter">
<opener>
<dateline>
<date when="1982-09-25">
9-25-82</date>
</dateline>
<salute>Dear Theressa</salute>
</opener>
<note>
<p>Did I spell your name right?</p>
<action>(Smile)</action>
<p>Well right now I'm tired been replanting my plants, and house cleaning. You should see my kitchen it need cleaning bad. Hope you are feeling fine. 
<persName ref="#Dr_Winker">Dr Winker</persName>
gave me some pills my tail bone is better but they make me sick at the stomack. So I’ll take a less []loss?]
<persName ref="Marylyn">Marylyn</persName>
haven’t had her baby yet. I guess everyone and everything is about the same
</p>
<p>
Here is a clean joke because I washed it.
<joke>The youngsters in a Sunday school class were asked to name their favorite Biblical character.. The little boy said, King Solomon! Why? Asked the teacher. Because he was kind to women and animals, he said. Who told you that? Everied (?) the teacher. Nobody, replied the boy, “The Bible says King Solomon kept 700 wives and 300 porcupines.
</joke>
</p>
<p>
<persName ref="#Ken_Freeman">Ken</persName>
is so proud of his football suit, I hope it will play a small part in him growing up even if he is babyed at home.
</p>
<p>
<persName ref="#Gearl">Gearl</persName>
and family all come over one nite this week, all but 
<persName ref="#Raymon">Raymon</persName>
You should see little 
<persName ref="#Trina_Logan">Tree</persName>
she try to talk back at 
<persName ref="#Gena_Logan">Gena.</persName>
<persName ref="#Gearl">Gearl</persName> said she have about broke up ever thing over there 
<persName ref="#Gena_Logan">Gena</persName>
is going back to Phill to go to school.
</p>
<p>One of 
<persName ref="#Jim_Culbertson">Jim Culbertson's</persName>
cows got out yesterday got in my garden that is what's left of it. I got the yard broom and went out there. I said GET, she turned and looked at me and I GOT I mean in the house and closed the door. I watched her out the window
</p>
<p>
I'm writing 
<persName ref="#Bobby_Logan">Bobby</persName>
and I put your address in it. I hope you hear from him.</p>
</note>
<note>
<dateline>
<date when="1982-09-25">
9-25-82</date>
</dateline>
<p>Boy it’s cold today. I’m sitting in front of the heater. Sunday school was the same my helper today is taking lots upon herself that I don’t like, but I’m going to let her dig her grave to tall in they look out for each other. The browns, the Wilkerson girls wasn’t at church today. Wonder how they got away from
<persName ref="#Frances">Frances?</persName>
I'm planning to have 
<persName ref="#Rev_Carpenter">Rev Carpenter and </persName>
<persName ref="#Ann">Ann,</persName>
<persName ref="#Tom">Tom</persName>
and
<persName ref="#Hester">Hester</persName>
for breakfast Sunday.
That's a big laugh. I bet 
<persName ref="#Hester">Hester</persName>
and
<persName ref="#Tom">Tom</persName>
wont come because I'm going to do most of the cooking.
</p>
<p>
<joke>A middle-aged father read that he shouldn’t mow the lawn in 90 degree heat, so he called his teenage son and said, “It says in this magazine that a man my age shouldn’t mow the lawn in the heat, I could have a heart attack. Will you do it for me? “ Sure, Pop, no problem” replied the teenager. The father had a heart attack.
</joke>
Well its dark and I'm already sleepy and I slep[t] this PM, you know how lazy people are. I feel like I'm going to be sick I hope not.
</p>
</note>
<closer>
<p>I love you
<advice> just keep pushing on you'll make it. Then you'll look back on this and be so very proud.
</advice>
I'm calling about the music next week
</p>
<p>See you</p>
<p>Love always</p>
<signed>Mary</signed>
</closer>
</div>
</body>
</text>
</TEI>